financialcontent.com 2011-12-31

# Stock Quote Widgets, Web Services, and XML Data API's for websites

## Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy is two-fold as it applies to the business customers that are registered to distribute our content and to the end users who may register in order to customize our content for individual use.

### Business Customers

All information obtained from business customers will be used only for the management of the accounts themselves. In no event will such information be given or sold to third parties unless required by law or if FinancialContent as a company is sold in its entirety. In the event of such a sale, the privacy policy will continue to be enforced if and only if the service continues to be offered. Otherwise, all information will be sealed and restricted from further business use and will thenceforth be stored for archival purposes only, such as account reconciliation and government audits. 

### End Users

All information obtained from end users will be used only for the customization of individual preferences. In no event will such information be given or sold to third parties unless required by law or FinancialContent as a company is sold in its entirety. In the event of such a sale, the privacy policy will continue to be enforced if and only if the service continues to be offered. Otherwise, all information will be destroyed.

### Cookie Policy

This website and the content modules that are distributed to its business customers use browser-based cookies to retain preferences submitted by business customers and end users for their convenience. The technology is noninvasive and does not identify any user beyond the account name selected by the user. 

### Choice/Opt Out

We use third-party companies to serve advertisements and collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this website, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about the practices of some of these third party advertising companies and learn which of these companies allow you to opt-out of this type of information collection, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp#). 

### Information Use

FinancialContent will use all information gathered in its totality only to improve the service being offered. Any additional products, services or special offers that will be presented to the users will not be targeted to specific users, but presented to all users.

### Important Disclaimer

Please note that while our company will make its best effort to uphold privacy, we cannot control external events that may compromise your anonymity - i.e., use of our website in a public library or Internet cafe, snooping software that sniffs TCP/IP packets, businesses that track employee usage on their intranets, etc.
